wiwigo.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - wiwigo.com | Wiwigo Technologies

This privacy policy sets out how Wiwigo uses and protects any information that you give Wiwigo when you use this website.

Wiwigo is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Wiwigo may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

#### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address and telephone number
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * nternal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

#### How to edit user information or log out?

The access to users account is through user ID login and passwords and Wiwigo persuades that the user promptly updates information if it changes in order to help Wiwigo keep the information up to date. The access would be withdrawn if such facility is not to be continued. Wiwigo keeps track of past transactions, therefore the User cannot delete information or opt-out of information associated with past transactions on the website.

#### Disclaimer

Every effort has been made to ensure that the information on this site is correct and up to date, however, Wiwigo does not provide any warranty as to the completeness or accuracy of the information and, subject to applicable laws, does not accept any liability for damages of any kind resulting from the access or use of this website and its contents. All information on this site is protected by copyright and other intellectual property rights. No images, text or other content from this site may be distributed or reproduced without prior written approval from Wiwigo.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information on the Contact Us page.
